<schema name="riddle">
    <system>
        You will learn how to answer questions by studying a few example interactions. Analyze the provided examples carefully, identify the underlying patterns, reasoning approach, and response structure. Then apply these insights to solve a new, unseen question.
        For the upcoming interaction, I will provide you with several example question-answer pairs to demonstrate the desired response style and reasoning method. After studying these examples, you will be asked to answer a new question using the same approach.
    </system>
    <user>
        Answer the last question.
    </user>
    <assistant>
        I understand. I will carefully examine the example interactions, extract the key principles and patterns of response, and then apply this learned approach to the new question. Please provide the example question-answer pairs.
    </assistant>

  <module name="module_1">
     Question: A man is incarcerated in prison, and as his punishment he has to carry a one tonne bag of sand backwards and forwards across a field the size of a football pitch.  What is the one thing he can put in it to make it lighter?
Choices: (A) throw (B) bit (C) gallon (D) mouse (E) hole
Output: hole
  </module>

  <module name="module_2">
     Question: What gets smaller as it gets fuller?
Choices: (A) bit (B) put (C) hole (D) rice (E) unit
Output: hole
  </module>

  <module name="module_3">
     Question: Whats weightless, visible to the naked eye, and when you put it in a barrel of water it will make the barrel lighter in weight. ?
Choices: (A) amoeba (B) vision (C) hole (D) hydride (E) canthus
Output: hole
  </module>

  <module name="module_4">
     Question: what is weightless, and colorless. . but when put into a barrel the barrel weighs less.  what am i?
Choices: (A) hole (B) measuring (C) heft (D) color (E) gallon
Output: hole
  </module>

  <module name="module_5">
     Question: What is lighter then a feather, can be seen by the naked eye, and when you put it into a barral, it makes it lighter?
Choices: (A) hole (B) find (C) dust (D) sclera (E) turn
Output: hole
  </module>

  <module name="module_6">
     Question: I am always Hungery, I must always be Fed.  the finger i lick will soon turn red.  What am I?
Choices: (A) cyan (B) rust (C) maroon (D) flame (E) primary colour
Output: flame
  </module>

  <module name="module_7">
     Question: i have no life to live or die i have no legs to dance and no lungs to breathe yet i do all three what am i
Choices: (A) flame (B) motivation (C) songs (D) friends (E) aggravated assault
Output: flame
  </module>

  <module name="module_8">
     Question: You can't hear me but I'm not dead.  Who am I ??
Choices: (A) spiritualist (B) silence (C) hearing (D) sound (E) look
Output: silence
  </module>

  <module name="module_9">
     Question: What shrinks during the day but grows during the night?
Choices: (A) nightwork (B) root (C) shade (D) sigh (E) silence
Output: silence
  </module>

  <module name="module_10">
     Question: Say my name and I am no more.   What am I?
Choices: (A) fade into nothing (B) fade to black (C) what happened (D) where am I (E) silence
Output: silence
  </module>
</schema>